I'm half Filipino, Hannah.
And I hated it all of my life.
But because of you,
I fell in love
with my other side.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh-oh, if there's alcohol,
there's mischief.
So, this is just a joke?
You don't love me, pabo (dummy)?
Just kidding.
[MOUTHING]
(In Filipino) I love you.
- I realized--
- [GASPS]
So it's true!
You can understand Tagalog!
Hey, Kpaps, no going back
on your word, alright?
You already hired me
as your translator.
You'll still pay me
65,000 pesos, alright?
Okay.
Only if you can translate this
last phrase for me.
You still need translation
despite knowing Tagalog?
"Expensive profit."
Mahal na kita
(expensive profit).
Mahal din kita.
(I love you too.)
["GUSTO KITANG PAKASALAN"
BY JEL REY PLAYING]
[SQUEALING]
["GUSTO KITANG PAKASALAN"
CONTINUES]
Oh, you!
Of course, pabo.
Because what you've given me...
is worth more than 65,000 pesos.
You're priceless.
["GUSTO KITANG PAKASALAN"
CONTINUES]
[CHAIRMAN SONG]
No kissing!
[MUSIC STOPS]
You have to court me first!
[LAUGHS]
[GIGGLING]
["GUSTO KITANG PAKASALAN"
RESUMES]
[SQUEALING]
["GUSTO KITANG PAKASALAN"
CONTINUES]